Contact

2901 Ohio Blvd Suite 245 8038257103 (Mobile) angela.jensen@vitaldecision sinc.com

www.linkedin.com/in/angelajensen-rn-ceo-lnc-8656a877 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Nursing Hospitals Palliative Care

Angela Jensen, RN CEO LNC

Owner/ CEO at Vital Decisions a Medical Legal Consulting Firm / Legal Nurse Consultant

West Terre Haute, Indiana

Summary

I am a licensed registered nurse in the state of Indiana. I started a medical legal consulting firm. We support patients/families, law firms, healthcare providers/facilities, insurance companies and commercial businesses. As a plaintiff or defendant in a legal case needing clinical knowledge and expertise, we provide an unbiased factual review and assessment in merit. Services that Vital Decisions' team provides include:

- * collecting, reviewing, organizing, summarizing, bates pagenating, indentifying tampered/missing medical records
- * researching and integrating resources in briefs
- * chronological reports, detailed briefing and visual aides
- * assist with discovery requests
- * interogotory questions
- * locating expert witnesses, questioning witnesses
- * participate in depositions, arbitration, mediation and trial
- * prepare trial exhibits, evidence and visual aides

Totaling 14 years extensive nurse experience including 10 years of hospital nursing in oncology, med/surg, telemetry, wound care, orthopedics, physcology, trauma, palliative, PACU, clinical education, HIV expert and IMC. As a travel nurse I assisted a chain of hospitals change emr as an expert in electronic medical records then trained staff in new trauma unit. I went to their behavioural health hospital to implementing changes achieveing improved patient outcomes, staff safety and deyta scores. After helping a neighbor in his home, hospice became my love. Hired as a prn field nurse, three months later, was promoted to clinical supervisor and mentored in administration. 2 years later, I was granted the opportunity as an administrator for a healthcare company, responsible for a start up site. I'm proud to say that this developed into the fastest growing site in the company, exceeding expectations by years. I am proficient in federal/state regulations, Medicare COP's, budget development/

adherence, building strong/competent staff, quality management, audits, surveys, accreditation and marketing.

Experience

PruittHealth
Director Of Health Services Hospice
December 2019 - Present (8 months)
South Carolina, United States

Vital Decisions, LLC Owner July 2018 - Present (2 years 1 month) Terre Haute, Indiana

Legal Nurse Consultanting Firm

VMS BioMarketing Clinical Educator June 2018 - Present (2 years 2 months) Region 8 Indiana

HIV AWARE- educating physicians, NPs, PAs, nurses and other clinicians on the potential HIV crisis in Indiana connected to the opioid abuse, rural population, ECT. I am enjoying the opportunity to contract with an amazing company, creating my own schedule, earning potential while fighting for the health safety of my community.

Looking For A Hospice Family
Hospice Administrator, RN
May 2018 - Present (2 years 3 months)
Terre Haute, Indiana willing to relocate by the water

Intrepid USA Healthcare Services Administrator March 2016 - May 2018 (2 years 3 months) Terre Haute, Indiana

Hospice Administrator

Gentiva Hospice Manager of Clinical Practice RN February 2014 - March 2016 (2 years 2 months)

Terre Haute

Medical Solutions registered nurse January 2013 - August 2013 (8 months) Fort Wayne, Indiana

Trauma/ Surgical/ tele as a travel nurse. Helped with conversion to Epic Computer Charting.

Behavioral Health Hospital as a travel nurse. In charge of staff duties and nursing group therapy.

Terre Haute Regional Hospital Staff Nurse RN Medical/oncology, tele April 2007 - June 2013 (6 years 3 months) Terre Haute Indiana

Education

Purdue University

American/U.S. Law/Legal Studies/Jurisprudence · (2019 - 2020)

Ivy Tech Community College
Associate of Science (AS), Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse